One of the experiences I had learned from AI
was learning about the
software that is
used in, like, the post -processing, post -processing
of EBSD data, so like using Kikuchi Pi
especially,
because it helped me to learn what the different
parameters do and how, and it showed me step
by step how it got a specific
output, and then from there, I was able to learn
how I can change the parameters on my own to
come up with different outputs and understand
what effect the changing the parameters
have on what
on the quality and the
accuracy of the of the map.
So that was really helpful because I was able
to learn things I didn't know, see an example
of how it carried out what I wanted to do,
and I could go and apply what I learned and do
what I wanted to do. Cool.
There's been several things similar that we're
interacting with this, helped me like understand
different parts of what we're doing in the lab.
So specifically with the lab setup and the atomizer
and like the safety but
side of that,
understanding the different things that can be
done to minimize static discharge for
dust explosions and also understanding the different
things that can be done to minimize static discharge
for dust explosions and also understanding
the
the best alloys we can get for the different
elements that we're trying to create into the
lab because several of them are, it turns out
they're like extremely explosive or reactive
with oxygen in their, when they're just in their
elemental form. Yeah. And so having them as aluminum
alloys, um, stabilizes them significantly and
they make them safer to handle.
That's cool. And so that was something recently
I learned about with there.
Anything else?
Can give more examples, I guess.
Um.
But do we need more? No, I think that's good.